We're constantly competing for the same
resources which made scaling our team
almost
impossible. When we first heard it was
available in Australia, we had to jump
on the
opportunity. Within just a few weeks, we
found that the candidate was supporting
customers and projects very
successfully.
This program is changing the way that we
construct our business central teams.
The BC talent team have our interests at
heart and I really think this is a
partnership of unlimited potential. It
enables us to get consultants that have
industry experience and also are trained
up in business central. It brings
consultants up to speed really quickly.
It also helps taking the pressure off
the existing team because the structure
of the program supports the person
coming in and they get good education.
The first two that we've had through it
been a great success. So now it's all
in. I see a future where the BC talent
program is a critical component of the
enablement strategy of all business
central partners whether it be upskill
whether it be reskill whether it be
recruit. This has to be part of what you
think about and offer to your team
members.